

DEVI JAGANNADH

CYBER SECURITY ENTHUSIASTIC

CONTACT

Phone: 9491376372

Email: devijagannadh@gmail.com

Web: www.thedj.tech

PROFILE

I am a vibrant individual who love to explore the magnificent subject cybersecurity. Every day, I try to explore new things in Networking world, I was proud white hat hacker who protects world against hackers and cyber attacks. Making an impact in the world through my works has been my passion and now I want to take the lead to ace in it.

PROJECTS

- WebHunt A CTF Platform
- A Personal VPN service in cloud using openVPN.
- Load balancer with 7 web servers in AWS.
- WiFi snooping system using Arduino .
- · Fingerprint Door Unlocking System.
- Gesture controlled car using Arduino.
- Online quiz portal using PHP with secure login.
- A Security audit report generator using PWN-DOC in AWS.
- Automated tutorial for Kali Linux tools using bash.
- Cyber-Twin & 6G (Currently working)
- Malware detecting using deep learning (Currently working)

SKILLS

- Ethical hacking
- Web application pen testing
- VAPT
- Network security
- Bash scripting and automation
- Cloud computing
- Secure coding
- Software development
- Network programming
- SQL and NoSQL database management
- Defensive and offensive tools
- Malware Development (Ethical)
- Cryptography
- Java
- Basic Python
- Researching
- Web development

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pen Tester

FRESH DIGITAL CONSULTING SERVICES JAN 2021 - MAY 2021 (PAID)

- Web Application Pen Testing on a Live Site
- Managing Team
- Detecting Bugs
- Exploiting Vulnerabilities
- Reporting

Red Team Pen Tester

FRESH DIGITAL CONSULTING SERVICES NOV 2020 - DEC 2020 (PAID)

- Web Application Pen Testing on a Live Site
- Detecting Bugs
- Exploiting Vulnerabilities
- Reporting

Vice President

NULL (INFOSEC) CHAPTER - VIT AP OCT 2020 - PRESENT (NON-PAID)

- Departments management
- Working on technical projects
- Conducting events
- Strategizing
- Collaborations and partnerships

EDUCATION

B.Tech Computer Science Engineering Sp. in Networking and Security

VELLORE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, AP 2018 - 2022 CGPA: 8.91

Intermediate - MPC

NARAYANA JUNIOR COLLEGE JUL 2016 - APR 2018 CGPA: 9.24

10 th Grade - CBSE

KAVIRAYANI PUBLIC SCHOOL JUN 2015 - JUN 2016 CGPA: 8.0